为了完成这个列表项 我们创建了一个水平的带有三个子View的LinearLayout。
To build up this list item we created a horizontal linear layout with three
第一个子View是ImageView，第二个子View是一个
children. The first child is an image view. The second child is a vertical
由两个互相叠起来的TextView组成的垂直LinearLayout
linear layout composed of two text views stacked on top of each other.
第三个也一样，是一个由两个
The third child is the same. It's a vertical linear layout composed of
显示温度的TextView叠起来的垂直LinearLayout。
the two temperature text views stacked on top of each other.
现在你可能疑惑为什么我们不用RelativeLayout。
Now you might be wondering why we didn't use a relative layout.
因为这样会使用较少的层级。是的，如果你想要
Because that would give us less layers of hierarchy. Well, relative layouts
指定一个view在另一个view的右边或者
are good if you want to specify that one view should be to the right of another,
上面的时候，使用RelativeLayout是合适的。当你想要一个view在
or on top of another view. Relative layouts are also good if you want a view to
父view的左边，上面，右边或者底部的时候RelativeLayout也很恰当。但对于现在这种，要让两个TextView居中于
be aligned to the parents left, top, right or bottom. But it's harder in this
在由ImageView分配的垂直高度中的情况而言，则会变得困难。
case to center these two text views within the vertical height allocated by this
在这里和这里使用LinearLayout都相对比较简单，所以不管这个图片是任何高度
image view. It's easier with the linear layout here and here, so if the image
这两个TextView仍然可以垂直方向居中
was any taller, these two text views would still stay vertically centered. And
这是在Android Studio中预览的样子
this is what it looks like in the Device Preview within Android Studio.
关于这个水平LinearLayout，我想指出一点，他有三个子视图的水平，
I want to point out one thing about this horizontal linear layout,
ImageView，垂直的LinearLayout和另外一个
which has three children. The image view, the vertical linear layout, and
垂直的LinearLayout。其中第二个子view实际上width设为0dp
the other vertical linear layout. The second child actually has a width of zero
但weight是1。那代表任何没有被其他子view占据的水平空间
DP but a weight of one. That means that any horizontal space that's not taken up
将会在设了weight的view中分配。
by other children will be distributed among views that have assigned weights. So
因此，来看一下第三个子view，它的宽度属性是wrap_content，weight属性为0
if we look at this third child, it has a width of wrap content and
如果我们把它的weight属性改为1
a weight of zero. If we gave it a weight of one,
它会被像这样拉伸。基本上这个图标是一个固定的宽度
then it would stretch out like this. Basically the icon is a fixed width, and
然后剩余的水平空间分给这两个子视图。
then the remaining horizontal space is divided among these two children.
因为他们都有属性weight为1，所以会平均分配。但是如果你看一下
Since they both have a weight one, it's distributed equally. But if you look at
线框图的话，这些温度视图是右对齐的。
the wire frames, these temperature views are actually aligned to the right. So
所以我们要做的就是把width的属性设置为wrap_content，weight属性设置为0
all we need is for the width to be wrap content, and for the weight to be zero.
然后任何剩下的水平空间就会给中间这个weight为1的元素。
Then any remaining horizontal space will be assigned to this middle element,
这是xml布局的代码。
with a weight of one. And this is the code for the xml layout.
我们有一个水平方向的LinearLayout。宽度是match_parent
We have a linear layout in horizontal orientation. The width is match parent to
占满屏幕的宽度，并且每一个列表项的高度为wrap_content。
match the width of the screen, and each list item has wrap content on its
但他有一个最小的高度，
height. But it does have a minimum height at least of this attribute,
值为listPreferredItemHeight。我们指定gravity值为center_vertial，从而让其所有的
list preferred item height. We specify gravity to be center vertical so that
子view都在竖直方向上居中。我们也设置了一点点padding
all of its children are vertically centered within it. We also specify a little
在他里面，我们添加一个ImageView，宽高都设为wrap_content。
bit of padding. Inside of it, we add an image view, which has wrap content for
并且我们设置src为这个占位的drawable。
height and width. And we specify the source as this placeholder drawable.
接着我们有这个垂直LinearLayout，宽为0dp，weight为1。
Next we have the vertical linear layout, where the width is zero DP and
我在这个View和他旁边的图标之间
the weight is one. We specify a little bit of padding between this view and
指定一点padding。在这个LinearLayout里面，
the icon beside it. Within the linear layout,
我们也有日期TextView和天气预报TextView。除此之外
we have the date textview as well as the forecast_textview. Beside that,
我们还有另外一个垂直的LinearLayout，包含了最高温度TextView
we have another vertical linear layout with the high temperature textview and
和最低温度TextView。就是这些。
the low temperature_textview. And that's it.